foreign
[Music]
open open open
foreign
[Music]
we got the student with us you know we
already went out to the club we got the
girls right behind us so we're gonna do
like a little after party here at my
house right now we're gonna just take
the party here at the mouse I actually
moved into the house and haven't done a
party so we're gonna pull up right now
and
what
bro I stole my lamb
cameras bro
who steals a Lambo in a neighbor who
does that
check your garage
check the garage
it doesn't matter right now what matters
is that you're about to change
somebody's life forget for the past two
years you've been doing what nobody in
this industry does traveling around the
world meeting these Traders and giving
free events giving them education
everything possible you have something
very similar to Rocket tuning one and
that rocket is different from every
other firm in the industry because they
actually care about the trades they're
number one firm that is community based
you've had other friends in the past and
you have left from the third time is a
charm that's why we decided to partner
up with you Alex on this deal that we're
going to be giving away a Trader Orlando
laughs
all right I had to take this mask off I
was tired as she was getting huh but
yeah guys yo turn the light on Jordan
turn up turn on yeah guys so we're
giving away my Lambo I did like a little
like movie cinematic stuff for you guys
like make it cool interactive you guys
know I like that stuff but I can't be an
actor we're literally giving my Lambo
away you guys want to know how this is
how
[Music]
yes you guys heard right I'm literally
going to end one of you guys in my
Lamborghini keys and the title 100 paid
off no taxes nothing all you have to do
is just put gas on it I'm gonna give it
to you guys with a full tank of gas and
no this is not a scam this is not uh sus
this is not anything you guys are gonna
see how when I explain right now how the
winner is going to be selected and how
the competition goes so you know how
rocket has a two-step evaluation to get
funded by the way they're adding a
one-step challenge soon but that's
completely off topic they have a two
evaluation process to get funded
so there's going to be a two evaluation
process to win the lambo giveaway so in
the second phase of evaluation there's
going to be 10 people selected to win
the lambo how do you become part of
these 10 people very simple the first
way is you register for the free
competition on their website it is
literally free you sign up you get
credentials and if you end up in the top
five of the leaderboard at the end of
the competition you move on to the
second stage it is completely for free
every single day you can go and you can
see the stats of where you are if you're
top 10 top 15 top 20 or if you're in the
top five so you know to maintain it so
at the end of the competition you are in
the top five you automatically move to
the second phase of the giveaway if you
don't end up in the top five you still
have a chance how so if you buy a rocket
21 challenge during the whole entire
month uh that the competition is going
on and at the end of the competition
you're not in the top five we will be
selecting five people at random from
anybody that purchases a rocket 21
challenge then those five people that we
select around and we'll do it live on
our YouTube or Instagram live they move
on to the second part along with the
five people from the competition so now
that we have the 10 people on the second
step of the giveaway what I'm going to
do is host a podcast or like a little
webinar with every single person and
we're going to put it in the rocket 21
Discord you guys should join the Discord
now so you guys already see all the
information that's in there and then
there's going to be a section that's
going to be Lambo giveaway once you
click on the lambo giveaway it's going
to have the 10 candidates that could
potentially win the lambo so I'm going
to do an interview with them get their
what why how just pretty much get to
know them and why should they win this
level right and then what are you guys
going to do every single one of you guys
that are in that Discord you guys are
going to vote for who should be the
winner of the lambo anonymously and
we'll probably have that going for six
ten days whatever we decide at the time
that is the most fair and as soon as we
close the the voting for whoever you
guys should vote that should win it's
going to be anonymous right you guys
won't know who's in the leaderboard or
who's not so it's not biased we'll close
it off and then we're going to host a
live event here in Miami it's going to
be a public event you guys just pull it
to Miami the 10 people and we're gonna
have a stage everybody's there we're
going to do the countdown pretty much
from last place to first place who wins
the lambo so we're literally going to
hand you the keys live here in Miami and
you're just gonna drive off of it so
this way you guys can tell that it's
literally legit we're gonna post the
amount of people that voted for the 10th
person nine eight seven six five four
three two one into whoever the majority
of the people voted for it's going to be
a public event in Miami as many of you
guys can pull up the same thing that
happened last time is not going to
happen we're gonna actually rent out a
full I'm talking about a full Warehouse
where two three thousand people can pull
up live and um this way the person like
it's just it's gonna be as real and as
raw as it gets so join the rocket 21
Discord there's going to be instructions
of who can participate and who can
obviously there's some countries that
you know you guys can't make it to the
states so you guys can participate in
the giveaway but they're going to be
another giveaway just for you guys on
the side for those of you that can't
make it to the United States which is
totally fine
um but yeah this is giveaway I think
this is the most authentic the most real
the most raw and I kind of want to give
you guys like the why like for me it's
giving back to the people you guys know
I do these events and get back to the
people all the time but
everybody's dream when they want to
become a successful Trader is obviously
you know pay off all their debt to help
their family but then get a landlord get
like a Supercar and get the stuff and
there's a lot of talks about there about
you know a lot of these firms not paying
people out being super scared it's a lot
of new firms pop up like every week all
these influencers they just make their
own firms and we like I was talking to
the team to the rocket team and we're
like dude if we give away a Lambo we
pretty much cash out quarter million
dollars and we just hand it to somebody
this is to show proof that rock is going
to have no issue paying you out there's
literally no issue shows the legitimacy
of the company of everything that is
done and just like innovating like we're
literally changing lives one person at a
time and I think it's the best way that
it could be done and it's my personal
Lambo like you know how hard I worked
for my land when the fact that I'm gonna
give it to somebody to me it's just like
nobody in this industry would ever do
something like this and personally
myself I think that as a person doing
this just makes me feel good and I would
I just want to see the reaction of the
person on the other side once I hand
them these keys in that title I want to
know what to do with it so let me know
what you guys think about this in the
comments below make sure you guys go
join the rocket Discord go check out the
website go check all this stuff because
all the updates are going to be inside
of there so hope you guys uh participate
I hope the person that wins is watching
this oh and by the way for the other
nine people that came to Miami and that
didn't you know don't win the lambo for
obvious reasons we're going to have a
cash prize for every single one of you
guys so um all I can say is
stay tuned oh and by the way another big
reason on why I'm doing this is because
I am the only person that is the most
verified when it comes to firms I am
literally here because of a prop firm if
I would have not got any payout three
three and a half four years ago from now
that made me leave my job at Dunkin
Donuts there would be no Alex G there
would be no YouTube there would be no
Lambo giveaway there would be none of
this stuff so I see a lot of these
people marketing these firms when
they've never taken a challenge never
passed an evaluation never got funded or
got a payout so it looks kind of like I
don't know to me it's very weird I don't
even get it to make any sense so this is
why I want to do this to not only show
you guys how legit rock it is and how
happy I am to be working with them but
on top of that that I am the most
verified person when it comes to firms
because I am here because of a firm I
didn't get rich off of an account flip I
never did it successfully I do it now
sometimes but I'm like the majority of
the time it doesn't go well for me so
this is the main also reason on why I'm
doing this because I am here because of
a prop firm and I want one of you guys
to be in the same position as me today
due to Rocket 21. all right so it's like
one in the morning right now nobody
wants to watch the car one in the
morning so I gotta pull up to these
touchless car washes
we'll get this one we'll get the best
one
payments yeah so pretty much we're gonna
wash the car now have some fun with it
I'm just gonna store it in the garage
pretty much until I the burnt into the
event like I don't plan to drive it
anymore until I hand the key to somebody
I don't think it's fair if I put miles
on it or I already put new tires on it
at the oil change so it's pretty much
ready to go to for somebody and I got a
new car coming in now I just traded the
G wagon for a Rolls-Royce so uh
is uh pretty much gonna be like one of
the last times that I tried
I'm good to go
[Music]
foreign